meehive.com 2010-09-27

# MeeHive: About

_MeeHive is owned and operated by Kosmix.View Kosmix's Terms of Service._

This is the privacy policy (the " **Privacy Policy** ") for the MeeHive online service (the " **Site** ") owned and made available by Kosmix Corporation (" **Kosmix** "). We respect your privacy and appreciate the confidence you have placed in the Site. We are committed to protecting your privacy and preserving your trust. Please carefully review this Privacy Policy to learn about how we collect, use and protect any Personal Information (defined below) and Non-Personal Information (defined below) you provide us on or through the Site and your choices for managing your Personal Information. This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms of Service posted on the Site.

## Opting Out Of Future Communications; Updating And Deleting Personal Information

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or wish to exclude your Personal Information from our direct marketing purposes, please tell us so at:

> Kosmix Corporation   
> 444 Castro Street, Suite 700   
> Mountain View, CA 94041   
> ph: 650-938-2300   
> fax: 650-938-5959   
> email: [legal@kosmix.com](mailto:legal@kosmix.com)

If you would like to update or delete your e-mail address, mailing address or other Personal Information with us please contact us the same way.

## Information We Automatically Collect

We automatically collect information that does not reflect or reference an individually identifiable user (" **Non-Personal Information** ") to help us understand how our users use the Site. Like most websites, we automatically collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files may include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the Web browser you used to visit the Site, the time you visited the Site, which Web pages you visited on the Site, and other anonymous Site usage data.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

We use cookies (a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your Web browser) and Web beacons (an electronic file placed within a website that monitors usage). We use cookies and Web beacons to improve the quality of the Site. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your Web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of the Site may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Certain of our Service Providers (defined below) and ad networks may use cookies and Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf, including, without limitation, targeted ad serving.

We may work with third-party advertising companies which may use information about your visit to the Site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you on the Site and on third-party websites. From the Site, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as Web beacons or pixel tags. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party advertisement serving company may collect from you. For more information about ad cookies and companies that provide users the ability to "opt-out" of the collection of information from such cookies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## Information You Choose To Submit

We collect information that personally identifies you, such as your name, email address, zip code, or other data which can be reasonably linked to such information (" **Personal Information** ") only if you choose to share such information with us. For example, you may be required to provide us with certain Personal Information to register with the Site, subscribe to one of our services, enter sweepstakes, contests or other promotions, and at other times. The decision to provide this information is optional; however, if you elect not to register or provide such information, you may not be able to access certain content or features or participate in certain areas of the Site.

## How Do We Use, And When Do We Share, Personal and Non-Personal Information We Collect?

We use Personal Information and Non-Personal Information for internal purposes, such as enhancing your experience at the Site; performing administration and technical support for the Site; notifying you about our new and existing content, events, products or services; enabling you to enter sweepstakes, contests and other promotions; and creating aggregated information about demographics and usage patterns.

We will not sell, share or rent Personal Information to third parties, and we will not otherwise disclose Personal Information to third parties, without your permission, except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

From time to time, we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours (" **Service Providers** "). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services including credit card processing, data management, promotional services, Web hosting, Web development, etc. We provide our service providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. Each Service Provider must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information involved in order to protect your information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.

We may share Personal Information and Non-Personal Information with entities controlling, controlled by, or under common control with Kosmix. In the event that Kosmix is merged, sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets, we may disclose or transfer Personal Information and Non-Personal Information in connection with such transaction.

In certain instances we may disclose Personal Information and Non-Personal Information when we believe it is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against persons or entities in order to protect Kosmix or our users or when we believe that the law or legal process requires such disclosure.

## Public Areas

Please be advised that, whenever you voluntarily post information to your profile or other community or interactive areas of the Site, such information can and may be accessed by the public. This means that any person or entity with access to such information can potentially use it for any purpose. However, you may have the option to make certain information private.

## Security

Information that we collect is stored on servers that Kosmix manages, using standard security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information in an effort to protect information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Site, we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit on or through the Site, and you do so at your own risk.

## Third Party Website Links And Content

The Site may contain links to websites or content operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked websites may be different from our Privacy Policy. You access such linked websites or third party content at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked website before disclosing any information on such site.

## E-mail Newsletter/Services

We may send you e-mails regarding the Site or a special promotion or event. All such e-mails contain an opt-out mechanism if you do not wish to receive future e-mails from us.

## Children's Privacy Statement

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.

## Policy Changes

We may, in our sole and absolute discretion, change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post a copy of the Privacy Policy as changed on the Site. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your agreement to abide by the Privacy Policy as changed. If you object to any such changes, your sole recourse shall be to cease using the Site.

Effective Date: 3/6/2009
